export const ADMIN_ASSESSMENT_QUESTIONS = [
  {
    id: 2,
    question_text: "What is the sum of the first 10 natural numbers?",
    question_paragraph: null,
    question_image: null,
    option_1: "45",
    option_2: "50",
    option_3: "55",
    option_4: "60",
    correct_option: "option_3",
    difficulty_level: 1,
    created_at: "2025-08-12T07:29:34.152095Z",
    updated_at: "2025-08-12T07:29:34.152109Z",
    subject: 2,
  },
  {
    id: 4,
    question_text: "What is your name select from the opton blow?",
    question_paragraph: null,
    question_image: null,
    option_1: "Ashish",
    option_2: "Veer",
    option_3: "Lavesh",
    option_4: "Saloni",
    correct_option: "option_4",
    difficulty_level: 1,
    created_at: "2025-08-18T04:22:36.123361Z",
    updated_at: "2025-08-18T04:22:36.123388Z",
    subject: 2,
  },
  {
    id: 5,
    question_text: "What is your sir name select from the opton blow?",
    question_paragraph: null,
    question_image: null,
    option_1: "Bishnoi",
    option_2: "choudhary",
    option_3: "kumar",
    option_4: "rathore",
    correct_option: "option_1",
    difficulty_level: 1,
    created_at: "2025-08-18T04:24:49.072317Z",
    updated_at: "2025-08-18T04:24:49.072335Z",
    subject: 2,
  },
  {
    id: 6,
    question_text: "What is your sir name select from the opton blow?",
    question_paragraph: null,
    question_image: null,
    option_1: "Bishnoi",
    option_2: "choudhary",
    option_3: "kumar",
    option_4: "rathore",
    correct_option: "option_1",
    difficulty_level: 1,
    created_at: "2025-08-18T07:22:12.267904Z",
    updated_at: "2025-08-18T07:22:12.267931Z",
    subject: 5,
  },
  {
    id: 1,
    question_text: "What is the sum of the first 90 natural numbers?",
    question_paragraph: null,
    question_image: null,
    option_1: "45",
    option_2: "50",
    option_3: "55",
    option_4: "60",
    correct_option: "option_3",
    difficulty_level: 2,
    created_at: "2025-08-12T07:27:42.897437Z",
    updated_at: "2025-08-18T07:34:28.974978Z",
    subject: 2,
  },
  {
    id: 7,
    question_text: "Sample question number 1: What is the correct answer?",
    question_paragraph: null,
    question_image: null,
    option_1: "Option A1",
    option_2: "Option B1",
    option_3: "Option C1",
    option_4: "Option D1",
    correct_option: "option_4",
    difficulty_level: 1,
    created_at: "2025-08-18T09:00:07.077327Z",
    updated_at: "2025-08-18T09:00:07.077353Z",
    subject: 5,
  },
  {
    id: 8,
    question_text: "Sample question number 2: What is the correct answer?",
    question_paragraph: null,
    question_image: null,
    option_1: "Option A2",
    option_2: "Option B2",
    option_3: "Option C2",
    option_4: "Option D2",
    correct_option: "option_2",
    difficulty_level: 1,
    created_at: "2025-08-18T09:00:07.748028Z",
    updated_at: "2025-08-18T09:00:07.748046Z",
    subject: 5,
  },
  {
    id: 9,
    question_text: "Sample question number 3: What is the correct answer?",
    question_paragraph: null,
    question_image: null,
    option_1: "Option A3",
    option_2: "Option B3",
    option_3: "Option C3",
    option_4: "Option D3",
    correct_option: "option_1",
    difficulty_level: 1,
    created_at: "2025-08-18T09:00:07.935302Z",
    updated_at: "2025-08-18T09:00:07.935324Z",
    subject: 5,
  },
  {
    id: 10,
    question_text: "Sample question number 4: What is the correct answer?",
    question_paragraph: null,
    question_image: null,
    option_1: "Option A4",
    option_2: "Option B4",
    option_3: "Option C4",
    option_4: "Option D4",
    correct_option: "option_1",
    difficulty_level: 2,
    created_at: "2025-08-18T09:00:08.156965Z",
    updated_at: "2025-08-18T09:00:08.156989Z",
    subject: 5,
  },
  {
    id: 11,
    question_text: "Sample question number 5: What is the correct answer?",
    question_paragraph: null,
    question_image: null,
    option_1: "Option A5",
    option_2: "Option B5",
    option_3: "Option C5",
    option_4: "Option D5",
    correct_option: "option_4",
    difficulty_level: 1,
    created_at: "2025-08-18T09:00:08.326201Z",
    updated_at: "2025-08-18T09:00:08.326219Z",
    subject: 5,
  },
  {
    id: 12,
    question_text: "Sample question number 6: What is the correct answer?",
    question_paragraph: null,
    question_image: null,
    option_1: "Option A6",
    option_2: "Option B6",
    option_3: "Option C6",
    option_4: "Option D6",
    correct_option: "option_3",
    difficulty_level: 3,
    created_at: "2025-08-18T09:00:08.497959Z",
    updated_at: "2025-08-18T09:00:08.497978Z",
    subject: 5,
  },
  {
    id: 13,
    question_text: "Sample question number 7: What is the correct answer?",
    question_paragraph: null,
    question_image: null,
    option_1: "Option A7",
    option_2: "Option B7",
    option_3: "Option C7",
    option_4: "Option D7",
    correct_option: "option_2",
    difficulty_level: 1,
    created_at: "2025-08-18T09:00:08.652701Z",
    updated_at: "2025-08-18T09:00:08.652721Z",
    subject: 5,
  },
];
